Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Since they took Osman captive ...
Karena mereka menangkap Osman ...
... they want information.
... mereka menginginkan informasi.
They think they will reach the treasure through it
Mereka pikir mereka akan mencapai harta karun melalui itu
Sir.
Sir.
What is your order?
Apa pesanan anda?
You will go to the castle as a messenger.
Anda akan pergi ke kastil sebagai pembawa pesan.
Say to them ...
Katakan pada mereka ...
... will give literary treasures.
... akan memberikan harta sastra.
Not that...
Namun ...
Usman ...
Usman ...
... on condition of release.
... dengan syarat rilis.
Sir...
Saya sendiri.
... we struggled so many years to get them.
... kami berjuang bertahun-tahun untuk mendapatkannya.
We martyred all our wounds.
Kami membunuh semua luka kami.
Is it worth for a Osman?
Apakah itu layak untuk seorang Osman?
We have taken back the reputation of Islam from them ...
Kami telah mengambil kembali reputasi Islam dari mereka ...
... Uncle dervish.
... Paman darwis.
But Osman, at least ...
Tapi Osman, setidaknya ...
... as valuable as the treasure.
... sama berharganya dengan harta.
Well, will we really give the treasure, sir?
Akankah kita benar-benar memberikan harta karun itu, tuan?
If we are going to take Osman, yes.
Jika kita akan mengambil Osman, ya.
I will be waiting for Yannis.
Saya akan menunggu Yannis.
Let's come with you, Dad.
Mari ikut denganmu, Ayah.
You...
Anda ...
... come to Kayi Oba, Bala.
... datang ke Kayi Oba, Bala.
If there is an important development there, let us know.
Jika ada perkembangan penting di sana, beri tahu kami.
A breath of the devil is in the oba.
Nafas iblis ada di oba.
If necessary, cut that breath away.
Jika perlu, potong nafas itu.
Your order is on me, my father.
Pesanan Anda ada pada saya, ayah saya.
Where do you go?
Kemana kamu pergi
We came from the ground ...
Kami datang dari tanah ...
... we'll go to the ground, girl.
... kita akan pergi ke tanah, gadis.
Come on, let us be blessed.
Ayo, mari kita diberkati.
Shoot ...
Tembak ...
... instead of blood ...
... bukannya darah ...
... you gush life.
... kamu membesut hidup.
Hope you gush.
Semoga Anda membesut.
Hit!
Tembak!
Talk!
Berbicara!
Where's the literary?
Di mana sastra?
If you don't speak, your alps too ...
Jika Anda tidak berbicara, Alpen Anda juga ...
... I will take your heart off with my hands.
... Aku akan mengambil hatimu dengan tanganku.
Talk!
Berbicara!
Come closer.
Mendekat.
SHE IS...
Dia ...
... where you want to disassemble.
... di mana Anda ingin membongkar.
My heart.
Hatiku.
And even ...
Dan bahkan ...
... in the hearts of all Turks.
... di hati semua orang Turki.
If your strength is enough ...
Jika kekuatanmu cukup ...
... take it off.
... lepaskan.
[Knife sound]
[Suara pisau]
Satan!
Setan!
Come!
Ayo!
Boğaç.
BOGAC.
No.
Tidak.
Boğaç!
BOGAC!
My brother!
Adikku!
Bey.
Bey.
Boğaç!
BOGAC!
I feel like a weak groan, Osman.
Aku merasa seperti erangan lemah, Osman.
Do you hear
Apakah kamu mendengar
Lions roar Sofia. It does not moans.
Singa mengaum Sofia. Ini tidak erangan.
Our dungeon ...
Kami dungeon ...
Osman, full of bones of decaying lions.
Osman, penuh dengan tulang singa yang membusuk.
Hang on, brother!
Tunggu, saudara!
Hang on! No swearing!
Tunggu! Tidak bersumpah!
Come on, God!
Ayo, Tuhan!
Boğaç!
BOGAC!
My God...
Tuhanku ...
... He says in the Baccarat:
... Dia mengatakan dalam Baccarat:
''Or...
'' Atau ...
... without encountering the ones before you ...
... tanpa menemukan yang sebelum Anda ...
Did you think you could enter paradise? ''
Apakah Anda pikir Anda bisa masuk surga? ''
Allahu Akbar.
Allahu Akbar.
Ornamental!
Diam!
Silence those dogs.
Diamkan anjing-anjing itu.
Allahu Akbar.
Allahu Akbar.
(Applauds)
(Bertepuk tangan)
Request...
Di sini ...
... picture of my perfect victory.
... gambar kemenangan sempurna saya.
Mr. Dundar ...
Pak Dundar ...
... those who do this job are obvious.
... mereka yang melakukan pekerjaan ini jelas.
Now you command. The alps of the beech ....
Sekarang kamu perintahkan. Alpen beech ....
... keep Kulucahisar castle narrow.
... pertahankan kastil Kulucahisar sempit.
Where do you take Kulucahisar from, Mr. Bamsı?
Di mana Anda mengambil Kulucahisar dari, Mr. Bamsı?
Sofia and Kalanos came to our obesity.
Sofia dan Kalanos datang ke obesitas kita.
they want friendship.
mereka menginginkan persahabatan.
We do not even know who did this treason.
Kami bahkan tidak tahu siapa yang melakukan pengkhianatan ini.
O Suleyman Shah's quarters!
Tempat tinggal O Suleyman Shah!
Who are your posts?
Siapa posting Anda?
Those who can not separate the friend and the enemy sit on their hide.
Mereka yang tidak dapat memisahkan teman dan musuh duduk bersembunyi.
I will cry that demon ...
Aku akan menangis iblis itu ...
... I saw it with the dust of my feet.
... Aku melihatnya dengan debu kakiku.
How can you not see the real face of Sofia?
Bagaimana bisa kamu tidak melihat wajah asli Sofia?
This is the song you pierce your tent ...
Ini adalah lagu yang kamu tendang tendamu ...
Unlike .... Selcan hatun.
Tidak seperti .... Selcan hatun.
The balance of this tip is sensitive ...
Keseimbangan tip ini sensitif ...
his politics is deep.
politiknya dalam.
If you hadn't run away with your husband before ...
Jika Anda belum melarikan diri dengan suami Anda sebelumnya ...
... you were your waistline.
... Anda adalah pinggang Anda.
Mind the mind, smear the language.
Pikirkan pikiran, aparkan bahasa.
Regardless of its diameter ...
Terlepas dari diameternya ...
... tries to teach us politics.
... mencoba mengajari kita politik.
Your age has passed ...
Umurmu telah berlalu ...
... Selcan hatun.
... Selcan hatun.
Ha...
Ha ...
If you try to get involved in our works ...
Jika Anda mencoba untuk terlibat dalam pekerjaan kami ...
... just know that I'm not cocky.
... ketahuilah bahwa aku tidak sombong.
Look at it, Bamsi ...
Lihat itu, Bamsi ...
... thinks the sultan who saw his strut.
... pikir sultan yang melihat penyangga.
Don't make me crazy and make yourself alms.
Jangan membuatku gila dan sedekah.
Let yourself come to Zöhre!
Biarkan diri Anda datang ke Zöhre!
Shut up!
Diam!
Selcan hatun.
Selcan hatun.
One of you in my assembly again ...
Salah satu dari kalian di majelis saya lagi ...
... if it gets longer
... jika semakin lama
... I cut your tongue.
... Aku memotong lidahmu.
Now...
Sekarang ...
Er square ...
Persegi ...
... let them leave.
... biarkan mereka pergi.
Look at your job.
Lihatlah pekerjaanmu.
Babes!
Babes!
Out!
Keluar!
Mr. Dundar ...
Pak Dundar ...
I said out!
Saya bilang!
... obviously there were those who forgot the wrath of beech at the tip.
... jelas ada orang-orang yang melupakan amarah beech di ujung.
Thesis, let's report their terms.
Tesis, mari laporkan persyaratannya.
Osman...
Osman ...
Osman is my child.
Osman adalah anakku.
Until I find him ...
Sampai aku menemukannya ...
... sleeping on our back, sleeping on our eyes is forbidden.
... tidur telentang, tidur di mata kita dilarang.
Not that,...
Namun, ...
... the game is bigger than I thought.
... permainannya lebih besar dari yang saya kira.
Usman ...
Usman ...
... to save him from the well ...
... untuk menyelamatkannya dari sumur ...
we will ambush like a wolf,
kita akan menyergap seperti serigala,
we will roar like a lion,
kita akan mengaum seperti singa,
like a fox
seperti rubah
... we'll be cunning.
... kita akan licik.
Now...
Sekarang ...
.. listen to me well.
.. dengarkan aku dengan baik.
(Laughs)
(Tertawa)
Great devil ...
Setan besar ...
...Welcome.
... selamat datang.
You pour in order.
Anda menuangkannya.
Our greatest pleasure ...
Kesenangan terbesar kami ...
Osman to make you suffer.
Osman membuatmu menderita.
We acted out the pain,
Kami memerankan rasa sakit,
... we became frustrated.
... kami menjadi frustrasi.
Don't be excited, Osman.
Jangan senang, Osman.
We have more time.
Kami punya lebih banyak waktu.
Your quotations ...
Kutipan Anda ...
... we will listen for a long time, Osman.
... kita akan mendengarkan untuk waktu yang lama, Osman.
Princess Sofia,..
Putri Sofia,
well done my beautiful girl
dilakukan dengan baik gadis cantik saya
The Turks will not be comfortable, ...
Turki tidak akan nyaman, ...
... they will look for Osman's trail in the castle.
... mereka akan mencari jejak Osman di kastil.
They keep on knowing you angel.
Mereka terus mengenalmu malaikat.
Don't worry, sir.
Jangan khawatir, tuan.
Come easy, Osman.
Ayo mudah, Osman.
(Laughs)
(Tertawa)
Mr. Gündüz ...
Tuan Gündüz ...
... we can't throw the claims into the wild.
... kita tidak bisa membuang klaim ke alam liar.
You..
Anda ..
... go to the castle with Mr. Bamsi ...
... pergi ke kastil dengan Pak Bamsi ...
... talk to Sofia.
... bicara dengan Sofia.
My anger ...
Saya marah ...
make them feel.
buat mereka merasa.
Say ...
Katakan ...
... in the incident of Osman's ambush ...
... dalam insiden penyergapan Osman ...
... if our friends have a finger ...
... jika teman-teman kita memiliki jari ...
... he cuts the finger, ...
... dia memotong jari, ...
... we take out your lungs.
... Kami mengambil paru-paru Anda.
This is yours, sir.
Ini milikmu, tuan.
May you exist, Dündar bey.
Semoga Anda ada, Dündar bey.
I wasn't done with that red nail anyway.
Saya tidak selesai dengan kuku merah itu.
You go for the salvation of Osman, Bamsı.
Anda pergi untuk keselamatan Osman, Bamsı.
Do not forget you.
Jangan lupa Anda.
both, we ...
keduanya, kami ...
... no account is left unfinished.
... tidak ada akun yang belum selesai.
Batu ...
Batu ...
... all around ...
... di sekitar ...
... where there is no place where their alps do not stand.
... di mana tidak ada tempat di mana Alpen mereka tidak berdiri.
Your eye is sharp, ...
Matamu tajam, ...
... your ear is the hole.
... telingamu adalah lubangnya.
Let them be everywhere.
Biarkan mereka ada di mana-mana.
A trail, ...
Jejak, ...
... if they find a man ...
... jika mereka menemukan seorang pria ...
... let us know.
... beri tahu kami.
Sacrifice your life, my father.
Korbankan hidupmu, ayahku.
I was waiting for you smarter.
Aku menunggumu lebih pintar.
Just in your first fight ...
Hanya dalam pertarungan pertamamu ...
... you fell into my net, Osman.
... Anda jatuh ke jaring saya, Osman.
You celebrate your victory early, Yannis.
Anda merayakan kemenangan Anda lebih awal, Yannis.
Our struggle is just beginning.
Perjuangan kita baru saja dimulai.
Thank goodness to my Lord ...
Syukurlah kepada Tuhanku ...
... a demon like you made me an enemy.
... iblis seperti kamu membuatku musuh.
Did you learn from your father?
Apakah kamu belajar dari ayahmu?
... fierce Osman.
... Osman yang ganas.
You want to know where Sheikh Edebali is, right?
Anda ingin tahu di mana Sheikh Edebali berada, bukan?
Selling it to you,
Menjualnya kepada Anda,
you want to find out where the treasures are.
Anda ingin mencari tahu di mana harta itu berada.
As a matter of fact...
Yang benar adalah ...
I don't even care about your treasures.
Aku bahkan tidak peduli dengan hartamu.
My problem...
Masalah saya adalah ...
... destroy your reputation.
... hancurkan reputasi Anda.
The precious of a nation ...
Yang berharga dari suatu bangsa ...
... if you take it ...
... jika kamu mengambilnya ...
... you will receive your honor and honor.
... Anda akan menerima kehormatan dan kehormatan Anda.
Or I have one of those treasures ...
Atau saya punya salah satu harta karun itu ...
... so much.
... sangat banyak.
Maybe you can take our treasure ...
Mungkin Anda bisa mengambil harta kami ...
...not that,...
... namun ...
... our soul never!
... jiwa kita tidak pernah!
The province goes ...
Provinsi berjalan ...
our ancestors said ...
leluhur kita berkata ...
We...
Kami ...
... honor our ...
... kehormatan kami ...
... we riveted our hearts and minds.
... kami memusatkan hati dan pikiran kami.
Even if there is only one Turk left on the earth ...
Bahkan jika hanya ada satu Turk yang tersisa di bumi ...
... our state means that our ceremony is alive.
... negara kita berarti upacara kita masih hidup.
He is also the purpose of a single Turk, your ...
Dia juga tujuan dari seorang Turki, ...
is to demolish the pharaohs.
adalah untuk menghancurkan para firaun.
Come on, Osman.
Ayo, Osman.
you're thirsty.
Anda haus.
You are very angry, novice Osman.
Anda sangat marah, Osman pemula.
Very.
Sangat.
Is it ready?
Apakah sudah siap
(Sword sound)
(Suara pedang)
Oh, fire.
Oh, tembak.
Iron mountains ...
Pegunungan besi ...
... the melting fire.
... api yang meleleh.
Show your strength!
Tunjukkan kekuatan Anda!
(Laughs)
(Tertawa)
(Sighs)
(Sighs)
Demon!
Setan!
Bastard!
Inglourious!
Demon melu.
Setan melu.
What good friends you have, Osman.
Teman baik apa yang Anda miliki, Osman.
As you hurt ...
Saat kamu terluka ...
... they are shouting.
... mereka berteriak.
Is this the sword of your fire, Yannis?
Apakah ini pedang apimu, Yannis?
Now, witness my victory, Osman.
Sekarang, saksikan kemenangan saya, Osman.
Negal to!
Negal untuk!
Where's the literary?
Di mana sastra?
Where is Literary?
Dimanakah Sastra?
God!
Tuhan!
In the name of Allah, the most gracious and womb.
Atas nama Allah, rahim dan rahim yang paling.
'' Certainly, we have given you a clear conquest.
'' Tentu saja, kami telah memberi Anda penaklukan yang jelas.
That Allah ..
Allah itu ..
... forgive your past and future sins,
... maafkan dosa masa lalu dan masa depan Anda,
... complete your blessing to you, ...
... lengkapi berkahmu untukmu, ...
... get you on the right path ...
... membawamu ke jalan yang benar ...
... and Allah for you ...
... dan Allah untukmu ...
... help with a glorious victory. ''
... membantu dengan kemenangan yang mulia. ''
SHE IS,...
Dia ...
... the beliefs of the believers ...
... Keyakinan orang-orang percaya ...
... for incrementally ...
... untuk tambahan ...
... hearts ...
... hati ...
... gives peace and security.
... memberikan kedamaian dan keamanan.
Armies of heaven and earth are God's.
Tentara surga dan bumi adalah milik Allah.
God...
Tuhan ...
... who knows it properly.
... siapa yang tahu benar.
Judgment and ...
Penghakiman dan ...
... has wisdom.
... memiliki kebijaksanaan.
Allahu Akbar!
Allahu Akbar!
Enough!
Cukup!
I will tell the place of Edebali.
Saya akan memberi tahu tempat Edebali.
I am listening to you, smart Osman.
Saya mendengarkan Anda, Osman yang cerdas.
Where's the literary?
Di mana sastra?
Master Yannis.
Tuan Yannis.
Come on, God!
Ayo, Tuhan!
Only God!
Hanya tuhan!
Genetic dogs!
Anjing genetika!
God!
Tuhan!
Sir...
Saya sendiri.
Master Yannis!
Tuan Yannis!
Is there any news from Osman Bey, Batur?
Apakah ada kabar dari Osman Bey, Batur?
Aren't you the cousin? You couldn't take care of a brain.
Bukankah Anda sepupunya? Anda tidak bisa merawat otak.
When you kneel at the enemy with your grudge ...
Ketika Anda berlutut di musuh dengan dendam Anda ...
... traitors inside us hit us.
... pengkhianat di dalam diri kita memukul kita.
I hope you have not betrayed again.
Saya harap Anda tidak mengkhianati lagi.
Otherwise, this time I don't feed your head to dogs.
Kalau tidak, kali ini saya tidak memberi makan kepala Anda untuk anjing.
You can't take care of your brain, but here ...
Anda tidak dapat merawat otak Anda, tetapi di sini ...
Sama!
Sama!
If you were so brave, while Osman was kidnapped ...
Jika Anda begitu berani, sementara Osman diculik ...
... what the hell would you do when martyrs died?
... apa yang akan kamu lakukan ketika para martir mati?
You are fever fever, Batur.
Anda demam, Batur.
But I have a word for Bamsı.
Tapi saya punya kata untuk Bamsı.
Until I kneel at the enemy, so that I will not carry wood to the mischief.
Sampai aku berlutut di hadapan musuh, sehingga aku tidak akan membawa kayu ke kerusakan.
If I hear another treason ...
Jika saya mendengar pengkhianatan lain ...
... if the sentence comes, I can not get rid of my neck from my tooth, you know.
... jika kalimatnya datang, saya tidak bisa menghilangkan leher saya dari gigi saya, lho.
You've long, Samsa, long.
Anda sudah lama, Samsa, lama.
You are going to the apricot now ...
Anda akan pergi ke aprikot sekarang ...
... allegiance to my father Dundar.
... kesetiaan kepada ayahku Dundar.
Our Ertuğrul Bey gave power of attorney to my father.
Ertuğrul Bey kami memberi kuasa kepada ayah saya.
God you're great.
Tuhan kau hebat.
You are great, my God.
Anda hebat, ya Tuhan.
What do I owe this visit to?
Untuk apa saya berutang kunjungan ini?
We didn't come for a visit, Sofia.
Kami tidak datang berkunjung, Sofia.
We came to ask for an account.
Kami datang untuk meminta akun.
An attack, maybe a betrayal.
Serangan, mungkin pengkhianatan.
You will tell us this.
Anda akan memberi tahu kami hal ini.
I don't understand anything from what you say.
Saya tidak mengerti apa pun dari apa yang Anda katakan.
What betrayal, what attack?
Pengkhianatan apa, serangan apa?
Osman bey and his alps were attacked.
Osman bey dan pasukannya diserang.
There is no need to extend the word.
Tidak perlu memperpanjang kata.
If there is Kulucahisar at the end of this melady ...
Jika ada Kulucahisar di akhir ...
... fear our wrath.
... Takut akan murka kita.
On our land, ...
Di tanah kami, ...
... you are threatening us in our pen, Mr. Gündüz.
... Anda mengancam kami di kandang kami, Tn. Gündüz.
We don't threaten, Kalanos!
Kami tidak mengancam, Kalanos!
Süleyman Shah's son Dundar is the command of the brain ....
Putra Süleyman Shah, Dundar adalah komandan otak ....
... If it hurt our Alps,
... Jika itu menyakiti Alpen kami,
... who mean our gentlemen ...
... Yang berarti tuan-tuan kita ...
... if you are the ones who take care of our health ...
... jika Anda adalah orang yang menjaga kesehatan kita ...
... the wrath of the beech will be on you ...
... murka beech akan menimpa Anda ...
... You know.
... Kau tahu.
God ...
Tuhan ...
... upon our faith in our patience ...
... atas iman kita dalam kesabaran kita ...
... we arrive at your door with our horses with lightning from their hooves.
... kami tiba di depan pintu Anda dengan kuda-kuda kami dengan kilat dari kuku mereka.
It washes your door with our iron fists ....
Mencuci pintu Anda dengan tangan besi kami ....
... we make tombstones from your zodiac signs.
... kami membuat batu nisan dari tanda zodiak Anda.
We do it, Sofia.
Kami melakukannya, Sofia.
We do billahi.
Kami melakukan billahi.
I understand your pain, Mr. Bamsı.
Saya mengerti rasa sakit Anda, Tn. Bamsı.
We are your strongest ally.
Kami adalah sekutu terkuat Anda.
Why should we do something like this?
Kenapa kita harus melakukan hal seperti ini?
We killed the traitor Yannis inside us.
Kami membunuh pengkhianat Yannis di dalam kami.
Just because our friend is getting stronger.
Hanya karena teman kita semakin kuat.
I lost my husband to make this peace.
Saya kehilangan suami untuk berdamai.
That's why,...
Jadi, ...
... whoever prevents this peace from breaking ...
... siapa pun yang mencegah perdamaian ini dari melanggar ...
... I kill with my own hands.
... Saya bunuh dengan tangan saya sendiri.
Commander Kalanos!
Komandan Kalanos!
It is my command to all soldiers in Kulucahisar fortress.
Ini adalah perintah saya untuk semua prajurit di benteng Kulucahisar.
Our strong ally ...
Sekutu kuat kami ...
Osman Bey, one of the lords of Kayı Obasi,
Osman, salah satu penguasa kayı obasi,
... will be searched everywhere.
... akan dicari kemana-mana.
It hurts him ...
Itu menyakitinya ...
... everything will be destroyed.
... semuanya akan hancur.
Until we get news from him ....
Sampai kita mendapat kabar darinya ....
... the movement will not end.
... gerakan tidak akan berakhir.
Yes, sir.
Aye.
Now stop your doubts about us ...
Sekarang hentikan keraguanmu tentang kami ...
... Mr. Gunduz.
... Tuan Gunduz.
As long as we keep the peace, everyone will win.
Selama kita menjaga kedamaian, semua orang akan menang.
Thank you.
Terima kasih.
Princess Sofia.
Putri Sofia.
Sofia ...
Sofia ...
... these eyes are there ...
... mata ini ada di sana ...
... these eyes ...
... mata ini ...
... dressed in lamb skin, and saw many foxes.
... Mengenakan kulit domba, dan melihat banyak rubah.
Finally, the hides of those foxes ...
Akhirnya, menyembunyikan rubah-rubah itu ...
... this has been sacked.
... ini telah dipecat.
Even if you ...
Bahkan jika Anda ...
...Princess Sofia.
Putri Sofia.
Come on, I'm Gunduz.
Ayo, saya Gunduz.
Let's be informal.
Mari bersikap informal.
Thank you, Mr. Bamsi.
Terima kasih, Tuan Bamsi.
Sir, sir are you okay?
Pak, apakah Anda baik-baik saja?
He even endured a lot.
Dia bahkan mengalami banyak hal.
As strong as a tiger.
Sekuat harimau.
He will not speak easily.
Dia tidak akan berbicara dengan mudah.
When it comes to you ...
Ketika sampai pada Anda ...
... continue to torture.
... terus menyiksa.
Where are you, sir?
Di mana Anda, tuan?
Fortress.
Benteng.
Literary will reach me for Osman.
Sastra akan menjangkau saya untuk Osman.
Don't let the men take the precaution.
Jangan biarkan para pria mengambil tindakan pencegahan.
Yes, sir.
Anda diperintahkan, tuan.
Kayi on ...
Kayi di ...
... smells blood quickly.
... Mencium darah dengan cepat.
That's the traitor Mark!
Itulah Markus pengkhianat!
Going.
Pergi.
Why did he come?
Kenapa dia datang?
What was he doing here?
Apa yang dia lakukan di sini?
Which face did you come here!
Wajah yang mana kamu datang ke sini!
What are you doing here Traitor!
Apa yang kamu lakukan di sini Pengkhianat!
Pastor Mark!
Pastor Mark!
Traitor!
Pengkhianat!
What are you doing here? There is a traitor, traitor.
Apa yang kamu lakukan disini Ada pengkhianat, pengkhianat.
What face do you come here?
Wajah apa kamu datang ke sini?
Kill the traitor!
Bunuh pengkhianat!
Kill it!
Bunuh itu!
Tursun Fakı!
Tursun Fakı!
Soldiers!
Tentara!
Get it!
Dapatkan itu!
(Sword sound)
(Suara pedang)
If you act, it will die.
Jika Anda bertindak, itu akan mati.
You will take me to Sofia.
Anda akan membawa saya ke Sofia.
I brought the greetings of Edebali.
Saya membawa salam Edebali.
Take meat, eat meat.
Ambil daging, makan daging.
Slow coyote, slow.
Coyote lambat, lambat.
You shouldn't die, you need me more.
Anda seharusnya tidak mati, Anda membutuhkan saya lebih banyak.
Why do you do that?
Kenapa kamu melakukan ini?
What do you want from me?
Apa yang kamu inginkan dariku?
Although our parties are separate, ...
Meskipun partai kami terpisah, ...
... our enemies are the same.
... musuh kita sama.
Osman.
Osman.
Listen to me carefully.
Dengarkan aku dengan baik.
This was Osman's trouble.
Ini adalah masalah Osman.
... a bigger trouble.
... masalah yang lebih besar.
Tell me where Osman is.
Katakan di mana Osman berada.
I have to protect my father's reputation.
Saya harus melindungi reputasi ayah saya.
Banane is from your father's reputation.
Banane berasal dari reputasi ayahmu.
I can't tell you where Osman is.
Saya tidak bisa memberi tahu Anda di mana Osman.
From you...
Senden ...
... not Osman's life,
... bukan kehidupan Osman,
I want your dead.
Aku ingin kematianmu
Osman,...
Osman, ...
... an obstacle to my dreams.
... sebuah rintangan untuk mimpi saya.
We go to the time, become the head of the hunt.
Kami pergi ke waktu, menjadi kepala perburuan.
Toykur becomes a halay.
Toykur menjadi halay.
Always, the most majestic Osman, the mighty Osman.
Selalu, Osman yang paling agung, Osman yang perkasa.
Me too...
Saya harus ...
I've always been left behind.
Saya selalu tertinggal.
Without going over it ...
Tanpa membahasnya ...
... I will not open up.
... saya tidak akan membuka.
Or ...
Atau ...
... I make a hole in your throat ...
... Aku membuat lubang di tenggorokanmu ...
... or ...
... atau ...
... I'll give you the gold in her lap.
... Aku akan memberimu emas di pangkuannya.
Nothing much to think about.
Tidak banyak yang dipikirkan.
You want me's head of Osman.
Anda ingin saya kepala Osman.
You just need to talk about gold.
Anda hanya perlu berbicara tentang emas.
I would even kill my father.
Aku bahkan akan membunuh ayahku.
I'll be waiting at the edge of the stream.
Saya akan menunggu di tepi sungai.
Bring Osman's head to me until evening.
Bawa kepala Osman kepadaku sampai malam.
Not that,...
Namun, ...
... no gold without seeing the head, you know.
... tidak ada emas tanpa melihat kepala, Anda tahu.
It was a good deal.
Itu bagus.
Nobody?
Tidak ada
You exist, son.
Kamu ada, nak.
Edebali!
Edebali!
Who more do you need?
Siapa lagi yang Anda butuhkan?
Where are you?
Di mana kau?
The creatures called human beings love ...
Makhluk yang disebut cinta manusia ...
son in your heart
anak di hatimu
Don't call me elsewhere.
Jangan panggil aku di tempat lain.
Thank god.
Syukurlah.
Edebali.
Edebali.
Our hands tied my arm.
Tangan kami mengikat lenganku.
I'm desperate.
Aku putus asa.
I have no strength.
Saya tidak punya kekuatan.
Those who find true freedom in servitude to Allah ...
Mereka yang menemukan kebebasan sejati dalam perbudakan kepada Allah ...
... they'll never be captured, son.
... mereka tidak akan pernah ditangkap, Nak.
Why is all this reason?
Mengapa semua alasan ini?
How do I get rid of this curse?
Bagaimana cara saya menyingkirkan kutukan ini?
Cure,...
Derman ...
... is in trouble.
... dalam kesulitan.
You will see.
Anda akan melihat.
Here, son.
Di sini, nak.
Get.
Al.
Separate dirt from mud.
Pisahkan kotoran dari lumpur.
Separate ...
Pisahkan ...
... learn to separate.
... belajar berpisah.
Find out ...
Temukan ...
... increase your knowledge.
... tingkatkan pengetahuanmu.
The real treasure ...
Harta nyata ...
... is science, Osmancik.
... adalah sains, Osmancik.
Treasures ...
Harta ...
but it is obvious to those who know how to see.
tetapi jelas bagi mereka yang tahu cara melihat.
Seeing everything, ...
Melihat semuanya, ...
... hear ...
... mendengar ...
God knows.
Tuhan tahu.
Do you think he forgot you?
Apakah Anda pikir dia melupakan Anda?
His servant came, do you think he tied you?
Pelayannya datang, apakah Anda pikir dia mengikat Anda?
Free your suspects, son.
Bebaskan tersangka Anda, Nak.
Separate dirt, ...
Pisahkan kotoran, ...
... to the treasure.
... untuk harta karun.
Fe inne meal ...
Saat makan ...
... usri yüsra.
... usri yüsra.
Fe inne ...
Di ...
... meal ...
... makan ...
... usri yüsra.
... usri yüsra.
Fe inne meal ...
Saat makan ...
Fe inne meal usri yüsra.
Setelah makan usri yüsra.
Honey chick!
Cewek sayang!
Be slow.
Lambat.
Your speed competes with your cheek.
Kecepatan Anda bersaing dengan pipi Anda.
If you put it through the door, you enter through the chimney.
Jika Anda memasukkannya melalui pintu, Anda masuk melalui cerobong asap.
What is this stupidity?
Apa kebodohan ini?
You do not know the ceremony as you do not know the limit.
Anda tidak tahu upacara itu karena Anda tidak tahu batasnya.
When was the guest arriving at the Turkish ceremony fired?
Kapan tamu yang tiba di upacara Turki dipecat?
I know what to say ...
Saya tahu harus berkata apa ...
... you don't know where to stop.
... kamu tidak tahu harus berhenti dari mana.
You came with your sinister feet ...
Anda datang dengan kaki jahat Anda ...
... you're in trouble.
... kamu dalam masalah.
Osman will die from your face!
Osman akan mati dari wajahmu!
How much more blood do you want?
Berapa banyak lagi darah yang Anda inginkan?
Not enough?
Bukankah itu cukup?
When you are in trouble, do you cry like that?
Ketika Anda dalam kesulitan, apakah Anda menangis seperti itu?
As if you grew up in the palace, not in the oba.
Seolah kau dibesarkan di istana, bukan di oba.
Aygül bacı, since you have big dreams ...
Aygül bacı, karena Anda memiliki impian besar ...
... then keep your heart big.
... maka jagalah hatimu tetap besar.
Don't fall like this in every fight
Jangan jatuh seperti ini di setiap pertarungan
If that hand is up to me again ...
Jika tangan itu terserah saya lagi ...
... I will scrape your eyes.
... Aku akan menggosok matamu.
Babes!
Babes!
Aygul!
Aygul!
What is going on in the middle of such a hall?
Apa yang terjadi di tengah-tengah aula seperti itu?
Trouble falls on us like rain, Selcan aunt.
Masalah menimpa kita seperti hujan, bibi Selcan.
Because of these.
Karena ini.
Now, without shame and boredom ...
Sekarang, tanpa rasa malu dan kebosanan ...
... they came to our door.
... mereka datang ke pintu kami.
Bala.
Bala.
Go late, girl.
Pergi terlambat, gadis.
Come on to your business!
Ayo bisnis Anda!
Lets!
Ayo!
Aygul.
Aygul.
You forget, I will remind you.
Anda lupa, saya akan mengingatkan Anda.
You're a gentleman.
Anda seorang pria sejati.
Your biggest ornament, literary. This is a.
Ornamen terbesar Anda, sastra. Yang ini
Osman showed his life for Bala chick.
Osman menunjukkan hidupnya untuk cewek Bala.
Nobody, including you, can get in between ...
Tidak seorang pun, termasuk Anda, dapat masuk di antara ...
... this is two.
... ini dua.
Earn these in your ear.
Dapatkan ini di telingamu.
Don't push my patience too much.
Jangan mendorong kesabaran saya terlalu banyak.
This is three.
Ini tiga.
What is this, Andreas?
Apa ini, Andreas?
To my presence with a priest breakdown ...
Kehadiran saya dengan gangguan imam ...
... what's it like?
... seperti apa rasanya?
HE?
HE?
Take it easy, Sofia.
Tenang, Sofia.
Your old friend came to visit you.
Teman lama Anda datang mengunjungi Anda.
What's going to get angry with that?
Apa yang akan membuat marah itu?
Soldiers!
Tentara!
If you take one step further, Andreas will die.
Jika Anda melangkah lebih jauh, Andreas akan mati.
I brought Edebali's offer.
Saya membawa tawaran Edebali.
Master Yannis was right again.
Tuan Yannis benar lagi.
Pastor Markos, ...
Pastor Markos, ...
... you came with your own feet.
... Anda datang dengan kaki Anda sendiri.
You will bring it to the treasure.
Anda akan membawanya ke harta.
I am listening to you.
Saya mendengarkan kamu
Until Yannis came ...
Sampai Yannis datang ...
... there is no single sentence.
... tidak ada satu kalimat pun.
I'll wait for him here.
Saya akan menunggunya di sini.
I hope I won't bother you.
Saya harap saya tidak akan mengganggu Anda.
Is there any news from Osman Bey?
Apakah ada kabar dari Osman Bey?
None.
Tidak ada.
No news ...
Tidak ada berita ...
... but they come out under the head of that red demon ...
... tetapi mereka keluar di bawah kepala iblis merah itu ...
...I know.
... Aku tahu.
Kulucahisar demons play us.
Setan Kulucahisar memerankan kita.
They do not know that the issue is not an account, it is a grant.
Mereka tidak tahu bahwa masalahnya bukan akun, itu adalah hibah.
You have to knock down that castle.
Anda harus merobohkan kastil itu.
Let Osman Bey return ...
Biarkan Osman Bey kembali ...
... it will be next time.
... akan lain kali.
I Uthman ...
Saya Utsman ...
... that's how God knows.
... itulah yang Tuhan tahu.
Osman is the fortune of our obese.
Osman adalah kekayaan orang gemuk kita.
May my Lord bless him.
Semoga Tuhanku memberkatinya.
My father sent me here when Osman got the brain news.
Ayah saya mengirim saya ke sini ketika Osman mendapat berita otak.
Do they have a wish?
Apakah mereka punya keinginan?
He wants to support.
Dia ingin mendukung.
God bless you.
Tuhan memberkatimu
Ah!
Ah!
You threw the conversation.
Anda melempar pembicaraan.
Do not mention the informal gentleman in this place.
Jangan menyebutkan pria informal di tempat ini.
Did you get unwanted in the binary output?
Apakah Anda mendapatkan yang tidak diinginkan dalam output biner?
Fe inne meal ...
Saat makan ...
... usri yüsra.
... usri yüsra.
Fe inne meal usri yüsra.
Setelah makan usri yüsra.
Fe inne meal ...
Saat makan ...
... usri yüsra.
... usri yüsra.
Thank God,
Terima kasih tuhan,
Thank god.
Syukurlah.
Lord!
Tuhan!
It is the first time that I see the lion who loves beating.
Ini adalah pertama kalinya saya melihat singa yang suka memukul.
And see your claw.
Dan lihat cakarnya.
Because Dundar became a proxy for the brain ...
Karena Dundar menjadi proxy untuk otak ...
... your lice got blood?
... kutu Anda mendapat darah?
Sir, sir ...
Pak, tuan ...
... I am informal, I am the chick of the apricot.
... Saya tidak resmi, saya adalah cewek aprikot.
If the syriad is floating ...
Jika syriad mengambang ...
... I bring it in line, insha'Allah.
... Aku mengantre, insya Allah.
There is no need for anyone.
Tidak perlu bagi siapa pun.
Good.
Baik.
You will start with your daughter first then.
Anda akan mulai dengan putri Anda terlebih dahulu.
The chick of the plane.
Cewek pesawat.
Dundar brain neither Edebali nor daughter ...
Otak Dundar, baik Edebali maupun putri ...
... he doesn't want it.
... dia tidak menginginkannya.
Whatever Mr. Bey says.
Apapun yang dikatakan Tuan Bey.
There is no beyond.
Tidak ada yang di luar.
Woe, woe, woe.
Terkutuklah, celakalah, celakalah.
When did you grow up enough to teach me the ceremony, Zöhre?
Kapan Anda cukup dewasa untuk mengajari saya upacara, Zöhre?
Teaching the ceremony to Selcan of the years ...
Mengajar upacara ke Selcan tahun ini ...
... if it is up to you ...
... jika terserah Anda ...
... wow that ceremony.
... wow upacara itu.
We...
Kami ...
You?
Anda?
The maid of being naughty ...
Pembantu menjadi nakal ...
... you mixed it up beautiful girl.
... Anda mencampurnya gadis cantik.
Now with your mom ...
Sekarang dengan ibumu ...
... think about what you've been doing all this time.
... pikirkan tentang apa yang telah Anda lakukan selama ini.
Think about...
Bayangkan ...
... Selcan hatun what a patient, understand.
... Selcan hatun apa yang sabar, mengerti.
As for Bala's line ...
Adapun garis Bala ...
... is my guest.
... adalah tamuku.
It has a place above my head.
Itu memiliki tempat di atas kepalaku.
Not an informal lady, but ...
Bukan wanita informal, tapi ...
... let the brain come ...
... biarkan otak datang ...
... can't touch my guest without breaking my corpse.
... tidak bisa menyentuh tamuku tanpa menghancurkan mayatku.
You know that.
Kamu tahu itu.
Not enough?
Bukankah itu cukup?
This is how you convey it to your brain.
Ini adalah bagaimana Anda menyampaikannya ke otak Anda.
As you said, chick.
Seperti katamu, cewek.
Whatever one does will make it to himself.
Apa pun yang dilakukan seseorang akan membuatnya untuk dirinya sendiri.
Inform yourself, you know what happens next.
Informasikan diri Anda, Anda tahu apa yang terjadi selanjutnya.
Zöhre ...
Zöhre ...
I have two feet ...
Saya memiliki dua kaki ...
... with your daughter ...
... dengan putrimu ...
... without taking those two feet under my feet ...
... tanpa mengambil kedua kaki di bawah kakiku ...
... go to your tent.
... pergi ke tendamu.
Don't boil my water.
Jangan merebus air saya.
While you have to go with your man, with your literature ...
Meskipun Anda harus pergi dengan pria Anda, dengan literatur Anda ...
... don't put yourself in front of the door.
... jangan menempatkan dirimu di depan pintu.
Lets!
Ayo!
Come on quickly!
Ayo cepat!
Hey!
Hey!
What is going on there?
Apa yang terjadi di sana?
Pastor Markos.
Pastor Markos.
To see you here again ...
Untuk melihatmu lagi di sini ...
how beautiful.
cantik sekali
As long as you stay in this land ...
Selama kamu tinggal di tanah ini ...
... you will see us every day.
... kamu akan melihat kami setiap hari.
Where is the treasure?
Di mana harta itu?
The object you call the treasure ....
Objek yang Anda sebut harta ....
Yannis is in the heart of everybody.
Yannis ada di jantung setiap orang.
No wonder you searched so much.
Tidak heran Anda mencari begitu banyak.
Does the literary want Osman,
Apakah sastra menginginkan Osman,
...does not he want it?
Bukankah dia mau?
Sir, he said he would give you what you wanted.
Pak, dia berkata dia akan memberi Anda apa yang Anda inginkan.
Where's the literary?
Di mana sastra?
You...
Anda ...
... is waiting around Akçadede.
... sedang menunggu di sekitar Akçadede.
Not that,...
Namun, ...
... if Osman does not see the right man ...
... jika Osman tidak melihat orang yang tepat ...
... sir will not bring the treasure.
... Tuan tidak akan membawa harta karun itu.
Nekal to!
Nekal untuk!
Bring Osman to the place he says.
Bawa Osman ke tempat yang katanya.
I will be waiting for you there.
Aku akan menunggumu di sana.
If this is a trap ...
Jika ini jebakan ...
... in Usman, ...
... di Usman, ...
... will die in Edebali.
... akan mati di Edebali.
Finally, you fell into my hand, Osman.
Akhirnya, Anda jatuh ke tangan saya, Osman.
You trapped us.
Anda menjebak kami.
Dog!
Anjing!
Like the canteen you put on my head as hangman ...
Seperti kantin yang Anda kenakan di kepala saya sebagai algojo ...
... I'm gonna kill.
... aku akan membunuh.
Kanturalı!
Kanturalı!
The teeth of the dogs like you do not pass to Kanturalı.
Gigi anjing seperti Anda tidak lolos ke Kanturalı.
Dundar is the son of a brain man, Batur,
Dundar adalah putra seorang pria otak, Batur,
... wants your head.
... menginginkan kepalamu.
Batur?
Batur?
Not only you...
Bukan hanya kamu ...
even the dogs around him are afraid of me.
bahkan anjing-anjing di sekitarnya takut padaku.
I see it in your eyes.
Aku melihatnya di matamu.
Your death will be so much fun.
Kematianmu akan sangat menyenangkan.
I ate, uncle's son!
Saya makan, putra paman!
Die!
Die!
Batur.
Batur.
Ah!
Ah!
Acıman!
Acıman!
Shoot without pain!
Tembak tanpa rasa sakit!
Lets!
Ayo!
Mr. Bamsi!
Tuan Bamsi!
Come on, God!
Ayo, Tuhan!
Samsa sergeant.
Sersan samsa.
Appreciate Allah!
Hargai Allah!
Come on, God!
Ayo, Tuhan!
My brother!
Adikku!
Batu ...
Batu ...
...What i say to you.
... apa yang harus aku katakan padamu?
Thank God you were brought up just in time.
Terima kasih Tuhan, Anda dibesarkan tepat pada waktunya.
Thank you.
Terima kasih.
How did you find it?
Bagaimana Anda menemukannya?
Huan ...
Huan ...
... fell into my trap.
... jatuh ke dalam perangkapku.
Bro who brought me to you.
Kakak yang membawaku ke kamu.
Forgive me.
Halal, hak Anda.
Good job.
Dapatkan halal.
Thank you, Mr. Batur.
Terima kasih, Pak Batur.
You played for the descendant of the shroud.
Anda telah bermain untuk keturunan kain kafan.
Brother!
Adikku!
Thank god.
Syukurlah.
Samsa!
Samsa!
Mr. Bamsı.
Tuan Bamsı.
Boğaç!
BOGAC!
Ahvali is bad.
Ahvali itu buruk.
Osman!
Osman!
Abdurrahman Gazi.
Abdurrahman Gazi.
I Usman.
Aku Usman.
Thank god...
Syukurlah ...
Thank God my father is back.
Syukurlah ayahku sudah kembali.
Brother.
Adikku.
My father?
Ayah saya?
Abdurrahman Gazi.
Abdurrahman Gazi.
Where is my father?
Dimana ayahku
Say, where's my father?
Katakan, dimana ayahku?
Our father is sick, brother.
Ayah kami sakit, saudara.
Non,...
Informal, ...
... power of attorney ...
... surat kuasa ...
... Dundar is in our uncle.
... Dundar ada di paman kami.
Hey gone years hey.
Hei, sudah bertahun-tahun, hei.
Hayme is my mother's smiling face.
Hayme adalah wajah ibuku yang tersenyum.
The full voice of Solomon Shahim.
Suara penuh Solomon Shahim.
The states of my Osman who are not in the palm of hand.
Keadaan Osman saya yang tidak di telapak tangan.
Ah.
Oh.
Sit down, what am I going to show you.
Duduk, apa yang akan saya tunjukkan.
These are my Osman's.
Ini adalah Osman-ku.
This cardigan.
Cardigan ini.
Tiny.
Sebuah kecil.
Oh, tiny.
Oh, mungil.
He was hanged at that time, now a lion.
Dia digantung pada waktu itu, sekarang singa.
I erected the first mane of that lion ...
Saya mendirikan surai pertama singa itu ...
...I.
... saya.
It grew and flourished.
Itu tumbuh dan berkembang.
He used pusat with Bamsı and Turgut bey.
Dia menggunakan pusat dengan Bamsı dan Turgut bey.
His bravery from Allah, ...
Keberaniannya dari Allah, ...
... took his skill in using pusat from his father Ertuğrul.
... mengambil keahliannya dalam menggunakan pusat dari ayahnya Ertuğrul.
He was always at the top among the children in Oba.
Dia selalu berada di puncak di antara anak-anak di Oba.
His arrow was stuck first.
Panahnya macet dulu.
He left the first wooden pusat.
Dia meninggalkan pusat kayu pertama.
Her peers also followed her.
Teman-temannya juga mengikutinya.
He grew up, became a gentleman.
Dia tumbuh dewasa, menjadi seorang pria terhormat.
Hunt friends as well.
Perburuan teman juga.
Fortunately, their relationship never deteriorated.
Untungnya, hubungan mereka tidak pernah memburuk.
Selcan hatun.
Selcan hatun.
There is something I wonder.
Ada sesuatu yang saya ingin tahu.
Ask me, girl.
Tanya saya, gadis.
Ask, don't be shy.
Tanyakan, jangan malu-malu.
Mr. Osman...
Osman Bey ...
Has he ever been in love before?
Pernahkah dia jatuh cinta sebelumnya?
I don't know that, girl.
Saya tidak tahu itu, nona.
But when I say Bala, I know the light that shines in her eyes.
Tetapi ketika saya mengatakan Bala, saya tahu cahaya yang bersinar di matanya.
I am Osman's mother.
Saya ibu Osman.
I know him well.
Saya kenal dia dengan baik.
If I mothered her,
Jika saya merawatnya,
... you know that ...
... kamu tahu itu ...
... Bala chick writes in the heart of Osman.
... Bala cewek menulis di jantung Osman.
It was heard from the sound of Bala that was shaking when he said chick.
Itu terdengar dari suara Bala yang bergetar ketika dia berkata cewek.
... and I can see it from its shining eyes.
... dan aku bisa melihatnya dari matanya yang bersinar.
Just like yours.
Sama seperti milikmu.
Apparently,...
Tampaknya ...
My Lord has tied your hearts together.
Tuanku telah mengikat hatimu bersama.
Good luck with you.
Semoga beruntung denganmu.
God willing.
Mudah-mudahan.
Thank God.
Terima kasih Tuhan.
Thank god.
Syukurlah.
My God ...
Tuhan ...
Osman forgave you.
Osman memaafkanmu.
May you exist, uncle.
Semoga Anda ada, paman.
You made my face slow ...
Anda membuat wajah saya lambat ...
... you bumped my chest.
... kamu menabrak dadaku.
With the help of Allah ...
Dengan bantuan Allah ...
... you saved Osman.
... Anda menyelamatkan Osman.
Be there, son.
Berada di sana, Nak.
Exist.
Ada
Long live Batur Alp!
Batur Alp live panjang!
(Sword sound.)
(Suara pedang.)
God bless uncle son.
Tuhan memberkati putra paman.
Uncle son from you.
Paman putra darimu.
Thank you, Mr. Dundar.
Terima kasih, Tn. Dundar.
Thank goodness the troubles that stifled our hearts have been resolved.
Syukurlah masalah yang meluluhlantakkan hati kita telah terselesaikan.
However, we are curious.
Namun, kami penasaran.
How Batur Alp got this job done.
Bagaimana Batur Alp menyelesaikan pekerjaan ini.
Selcan hatun through reason.
Selcan hatun melalui alasan.
Through the mind.
Melalui pikiran.
I have the key to save Osman, my father.
Saya memiliki kunci untuk menyelamatkan Osman, ayah saya.
Both ...
Kedua ...
... if we save him ...
... jika kita menyelamatkannya ...
... riveted in the beylik of Oba.
... terpaku di beylik Oba.
How?
Bagaimana?
The man called Hovan is in my hands.
Pria bernama Hovan ada di tanganku.
He will take us to Osman.
Dia akan membawa kita ke Osman.
Then press with Bamsı gentlemen.
Kemudian tekan dengan tuan Bamsı.
Zöhre ...
Zöhre ...
... I will take care of Osman.
... Aku akan mengurus Osman.
Aunt.
Bibi.
Those who do this to you ...
Mereka yang melakukan ini padamu ...
... drown in your blood, son.
... tenggelam dalam darahmu, nak.
Osman!
Osman!
When Gasp ...
Ketika Gasp ...
Come to the room.
Datanglah ke kamar.
Thank you uncle.
Terima kasih paman
Thank you.
Terima kasih.
I Uthman ...
Saya Utsman ...
... Honey chick is in the middle.
... Cewek madu ada di tengah.
What do you say, aunt?
Bagaimana menurutmu, bibi?
Lets.
Ayo.
Thanks.
Sağolasın.
The prisoners have fled!
Para tahanan telah melarikan diri!
Master Yannis.
Tuan Yannis.
We are going!
Kita akan!
I got out of hell,
Saya keluar dari neraka,
I fell on the slopes.
Saya jatuh di lereng.
My Lord rewarded him with his paradise ....
Tuanku menghadiahinya dengan surga ....
... honey chick.
... sayang cewek.
Every moment passed by begging.
Setiap saat berlalu dengan mengemis.
Thank god.
Syukurlah.
It was a privilege to see you right.
Merupakan suatu kehormatan melihat Anda benar.
God made me live the greatest of joys Osman.
Tuhan membuat saya hidup dari kesenangan Osman yang terbesar.
However, your condition is devastated.
Namun, kondisi Anda hancur.
Let your hands break!
Biarkan tanganmu patah!
Let the lineage out of those who do this to you!
Biarkan silsilah keluar dari mereka yang melakukan ini padamu!
You should be in the healing tent.
Anda harus berada di tenda penyembuhan.
Don't you know?
Apakah kamu tidak tahu?
Your words become an ointment to my wounds.
Kata-kata Anda menjadi salep untuk luka saya.
Your eyes light up my nights.
Matamu menerangi malamku.
Non,...
Informal, ...
I forgot my pain.
Saya lupa rasa sakit saya.
Forget it too.
Lupakan juga.
God,...
Tuhan ...
... with those who are patient.
... dengan mereka yang sabar.
Allah is with those who are patient.
Allah beserta orang-orang yang sabar.
Where is this Literary?
Di mana Sastra ini?
Or is this a game?
Atau ini game?
Be sure, ..
Pastikan, ..
Yannis is seeing you, sir.
Yannis melihatmu, tuan.
Edebali.
Edebali.
Soldiers!
Tentara!
The past years have been tired of you, Literary.
Tahun-tahun terakhir telah membuatmu bosan, Sastra.
Where is the young I see at the foot of Ahi Evran,
Di mana anak muda saya lihat di kaki Ahi Evran,
... where is the old man in front of me.
... di mana lelaki tua di depanku.
This depends on how you look, Yannis.
Ini tergantung pada penampilanmu, Yannis.
Young enough to fight you all the time ...
Cukup muda untuk melawanmu sepanjang waktu ...
I'm old as if he'll die at any moment.
Aku sudah tua seolah dia akan mati kapan saja.
Apparently these clacks did not help you.
Rupanya alat ini tidak membantu Anda.
Here you are.
Ini dia.
If you don't give what I want ...
Jika Anda tidak memberikan apa yang saya inginkan ...
... you know you'll die.
... kamu tahu kamu akan mati.
Those who perished in the right case ...
Mereka yang tewas dalam kasus yang tepat ...
... lives more than his executioners ...
... hidup lebih dari algojo ...
... Yannis.
... Yannis.
You won't give up, are you?
Anda tidak akan menyerah, kan?
The fighting spirit inside,
Semangat juang di dalam,
... makes you a warrior like a goat.
... membuatmu menjadi prajurit seperti kambing.
You don't even see the defeat based on the door.
Anda bahkan tidak melihat kekalahan berdasarkan pintu.
God ordered us to fight the oppressors.
Tuhan memerintahkan kita untuk memerangi para penindas.
Victory is both my blessing!
Kemenangan adalah berkah saya!
In our view ...
Dalam pandangan kami ...
... the head from it is about the eye.
... kepala dari itu adalah tentang mata.
What a pity.
Sayang sekali, sayang sekali.
You still believe that it will change the layout I set up.
Anda masih percaya bahwa itu akan mengubah tata letak yang saya atur.
Not just the order, but ...
Bukan hanya pesanan, tapi ...
... we will change the age, Yannis.
... kita akan mengubah usia, Yannis.
The persecution reign of you ...
Pemerintahan penganiayaan Anda ...
... will fall to the ground.
... akan jatuh ke tanah.
Huge....
Besar ....
... Suleyman Shah's grandson, ...
... Cucu Suleyman Shah, ...
...Osman.
... Osman.
To the wounds that open ...
Untuk luka yang terbuka ...
... take a good look.
... perhatikan baik-baik.
Look ...
Lihat ...
... see you tomorrow.
... sampai jumpa besok.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Sorry, your injuries Osman.
Maaf, cedera Anda, Osman.
Sorry ...
Maaf ...
... let your fire go.
... lepaskan apimu.
May you burn, Mr. Osman.
Semoga Anda terbakar, Pak Osman.
Let it be ...
Biarkan ...
... salute the good fortune.
... salut nasib baik.
To you ...
Untuk anda ...
... is your engagement.
... adalah pertunangan Anda.
Do not forget you.
Jangan lupa Anda.
You have not changed at all.
Kamu tidak pernah berubah.
Since we will wait for the Treasury and Osman ...
Karena kita akan menunggu Departemen Keuangan dan Osman ...
... faithful to you ...
... setia padamu ...
I would like to hear how you raise these guys.
Saya ingin mendengar bagaimana Anda membesarkan orang-orang ini.
Hearts are in the hands of God Yannis.
Hati ada di tangan Dewa Yannis.
In the profanity well you are in ...
Dalam kata-kata kotor Anda berada di ...
... you see this light ...
... kamu melihat cahaya ini ...
... it's impossible to grasp the truths of this commitment.
... tidak mungkin untuk memahami kebenaran dari komitmen ini.
I leaked to you.
Saya bocor ke Anda.
His skin belongs to you and his spirit to us ...
Kulitnya milik Anda dan rohnya milik kami ...
I raised hundreds of men.
Saya membesarkan ratusan pria.
The unity consciousness of Muslims is left behind, Edebali.
Kesadaran persatuan umat Islam tertinggal, Edebali.
You believe that you will revive that spirit.
Anda percaya bahwa Anda akan menghidupkan kembali roh itu.
With the gold I bought from you ...
Dengan emas yang aku beli darimu ...
I'm going to recruit new souls.
Saya akan merekrut jiwa baru.
I will hit you with yours.
Aku akan memukulmu dengan milikmu.
We are so brave that Yannis, ...
Kami sangat berani bahwa Yannis, ...
their soul has no cost.
Jiwa mereka tidak memiliki biaya.
What authority, ...
Otoritas apa, ...
... neither position nor any other world.
... bukan posisi atau dunia lain.
They are filled with dhikr,
Mereka dipenuhi dengan zikir,
... thankfully she dresses, ...
... syukurlah dia berpakaian, ...
they fight patiently.
mereka bertarung dengan sabar.
Sure, you ...
Tentu kamu ...
You are not even aware of this because it is the toy of the devil.
Anda bahkan tidak menyadari ini karena itu adalah mainan iblis.
Keep in mind,...
Ingat, ...
.... the previous name of the devil was Azazil.
.... nama iblis sebelumnya adalah Azazil.
Heaven's keeper, ...
Penjaga surga, ...
... and he was the manager of the angels.
... dan dia adalah manajer para malaikat.
Your destiny is the same.
Nasib Anda sama.
Who also demonizes you ....
Siapa yang juga menjelekkanmu ....
... your ambition to win, your pride.
... ambisi Anda untuk menang, kebanggaan Anda.
If there is victory in the end, I don't care at all.
Jika ada kemenangan pada akhirnya, saya tidak peduli sama sekali.
Alone, I wonder.
Sendiri, saya bertanya-tanya.
Why is this Osman so important to you?
Mengapa Osman ini begitu penting bagimu?
Otherwise, Ahmet Yesevi's wooden sword ...
Jika tidak, pedang kayu Ahmet Yesevi ...
... would you consider giving it to him?
... apakah Anda akan mempertimbangkan untuk memberikannya kepadanya?
Absolute fate, ...
Nasib absolut, ...
Yannis knitting his nets.
Yannis merajut jalanya.
The end of people like you,
Akhir dari orang-orang seperti Anda,
... will bring brave people like Osman.
... akan membawa orang-orang pemberani seperti Osman.
Osman...
Osman ...
I am Batur, sky-eyed brave.
Saya Batur, berani bermata langit.
God is always on his way ...
Tuhan selalu dalam perjalanan ...
... make your pusat sharp.
... buat pusatmu tajam.
Amen mom, be there.
Amin ibu, ada di sana.
Amine.
Amin.
Oba ...
Oba ...
... all balances have changed.
... semua saldo telah berubah.
God for every father ...
Tuhan untuk setiap ayah ...
... just like a son like you, son.
... seperti anak laki-laki sepertimu, nak.
Sacrifice your way, my father.
Korbankan caramu, ayahku.
He sent his literary daughter to the oba.
Dia mengirim putri sastra ke oba.
Keep Osman away from Sheikh Edebali, Mr. Dundar.
Jauhkan Osman dari Sheikh Edebali, Mr. Dundar.
Otherwise, we will not get rid of trouble.
Kalau tidak, kami tidak akan menyingkirkan masalah.
Girl,...
Girl, ...
... Is it in Osman's tent now?
... Apakah itu di tenda Osman sekarang?
Yeah, dad.
Ya ayah
I'm afraid he wants to marry Osman and set up in the bed.
Saya khawatir dia ingin menikahi Osman dan mengatur di tempat tidur.
It...
Ini ...
... kayı oba becomes a disaster.
... kayı oba menjadi bencana.
Lets...
Ayo ...
...Come with me.
Ikut aku.
Raid,...
Serangan ...
... belongs to the press.
... milik pers.
Good health Aybüke.
Aybüke kesehatan yang baik.
Bon Appetit.
Selamat menikmati makanan Anda.
Thanks.
Terima kasih.
Thank goodness our partner got peace.
Syukurlah mitra kami mendapat kedamaian.
Thank god.
Syukurlah.
Informal, if I take care of my Ottoman ...
Informal, jika saya merawat Ottoman saya ...
... I don't have eyes.
... aku tidak punya mata.
No, Mr. Dundar?
Tidak, Tn. Dundar?
I heard that ...
Saya mendengar itu ...
... Bala chick was here.
... Bala cewek ada di sini.
I would like to acknowledge this right with him.
Saya ingin mengakui hak ini dengannya.
Why did he come to that place?
Kenapa dia datang ke tempat itu?
This is what's going on ...
Inilah yang terjadi ...
Does it have anything to do with literary?
Apakah ada hubungannya dengan sastra?
Well, girl,
Baiklah, gadis,
How did your father reach the alps?
Bagaimana ayahmu mencapai pegunungan Alpen?
He dreamed.
Dia bermimpi.
Say,...
Jadi, ...
... he dreamed.
... dia bermimpi.
I wish he had seen it before ...
Saya berharap dia pernah melihatnya sebelumnya ...
... if the Ottomans did not lurk.
... jika Ottoman tidak mengintai.
It is Allah who saves and saves.
Allah-lah yang menyelamatkan dan menyelamatkan.
Bala chick says she knows.
Bala cewek bilang dia tahu.
What is it, do you not dream?
Apa itu, apakah kamu tidak bermimpi?
You talk about this issue face to face with my father.
Anda berbicara tentang masalah ini berhadap-hadapan dengan ayah saya.
Fortunately, my Lord, Osman forgave you.
Untungnya, Tuhanku, Osman memaafkanmu.
Thank god.
Syukurlah.
Thank goodness he has returned.
Syukurlah dia telah kembali.
However, this fight is told him again,
Namun, pertarungan ini diceritakan lagi padanya,
... or whether he will mean another soul ...
... atau apakah dia akan berarti jiwa lain ...
How do we know?
Bagaimana kita tahu
We, in this oba ...
Kami, dalam oba ini ...
... we lived in unity and vitality.
... kami hidup dalam kesatuan dan vitalitas.
All these melandas emerged with the arrival of Edebali.
Semua melanda ini muncul dengan kedatangan Edebali.
Uncle!
Paman!
I'll talk, Osman.
Saya akan bicara, Osman.
I!
Saya!
Oban ...
Oban ...
... gentleman!
... pria!
Now,...
Sekarang, ...
...everyone...
... semua orang ...
... you should know exactly what I said.
... Anda harus tahu persis apa yang saya katakan.
I am in my ob ...
Saya di ob ...
I don't want my union to be broken.
Saya tidak ingin serikat saya rusak.
I'm in this oba ...
Saya di oba ini ...
.... duality ...
.... dualitas ...
...I do not want.
... Aku tidak.
What we saw from our ancestor ...
Apa yang kami lihat dari leluhur kami ...
... dispersed ...
... tersebar ...
not to be miserable.
tidak menjadi sengsara.
Taking care of each other, ...
Merawat satu sama lain, ...
... is to be one.
... harus menjadi satu.
Non,...
Informal, ...
... think about us, Bala chick.
... Pikirkan tentang kami, Bala cewek.
This is enough.
Ini sudah cukup.
More trouble, ...
Lebih banyak masalah, ...
... we don't want to be a mess.
... kami tidak ingin berantakan.
As for you, Osman, ...
Adapun Anda, Osman, ...
... with that Literary ...
... dengan Sastra itu ...
... if you keep on doing business ...
... jika Anda terus melakukan bisnis ...
... you can't see our unofficial support,
... Anda tidak dapat melihat dukungan tidak resmi kami,
... even you.
... bahkan Anda.
Got it, Mr. Dundar!
Paham, Tn. Dundar!
May Allah keep all sorts of trouble and misery away from your oban.
Semoga Allah menjauhkan segala macam kesusahan dan penderitaan dari oban Anda.
Excuse me.
Permisi
Come on, Gonca hat.
Ayo, topi Gonca.
Osman.
Osman.
You've survived many trouble.
Anda telah melewati banyak masalah.
But now,...
Tapi sekarang, ...
... it's time to put your mind together.
... saatnya untuk menyatukan pikiran Anda.
Literary and daughter ...
Sastra dan anak perempuan ...
... dervishes ...
... darwis ...
... they brought nothing but restlessness to this oba.
... mereka membawa kegelisahan untuk oba ini.
Bala's chick ...
Cewek Bala ...
... this place has no place.
... tempat ini tidak memiliki tempat.
Uncle!
Paman!
How about you?
Bagaimana dengan anda
The dagger that opened the wounds ...
Belati yang membuka luka ...
... was in Sofia's hands.
... ada di tangan Sofia.
The evil spreads from the bosom of the shroud.
Kejahatan menyebar dari dada kafan itu.
What Sheikh Edebali ...
Apa Sheikh Edebali ...
... where the Bala line has an internal.
... di mana garis Bala memiliki internal.
Unlike,...
Sebaliknya, ...
... they are both our crown.
... mereka berdua mahkota kita.
Osman!
Osman!
You approach the crossroads, Osman.
Anda mendekati persimpangan, Osman.
Where you belong, ...
Di mana Anda berada, ...
... that's it.
... itu saja.
You know who's up for it.
Anda tahu siapa yang siap untuk itu.
That's why I just don't rebel!
Itu sebabnya saya tidak memberontak!
If necessary,...
Jika perlu, ...
... i'm going to slam!
... aku akan membanting!
You too ...
Kamu juga ...
that's how you memorize it.
begitulah cara Anda menghafalnya.
Honey chick!
Cewek sayang!
Calm down.
Tetap tenang.
If the whole world tries to take you away from me,
Jika seluruh dunia mencoba mengambilmu dariku,
... I don't bow to anyone, you know.
... Saya tidak tunduk pada siapa pun, Anda tahu.
I know, Osman.
Saya tahu, Osman.
However, no one should be in trouble because of us.
Namun, tidak ada yang harus dalam kesulitan karena kita.
No one should get a fire in the hearth.
Tidak ada yang harus mendapatkan api di perapian.
Ahis' head does not stay out of trouble.
Kepala Ahis tidak terhindar dari masalah.
The trouble that will come from you, ...
Masalah yang akan datang dari Anda, ...
... the victim of life ...
... korban kehidupan ...
... honey chick.
... sayang cewek.
Also,
baik,
Where is the literary?
Di mana sastra?
I will send my selcan aunt and ask you informally.
Saya akan mengirim bibi selcan saya dan meminta Anda secara informal.
He went to the Ahis.
Dia pergi ke Ahis.
Did he go to the Ahis?
Apakah dia pergi ke Ahis?
So what are you doing here?
Jadi, apa yang kamu lakukan di sini?
My father found it suitable, Mr. Osman.
Ayah saya merasa cocok, Pak Osman.
Honey chick.
Cewek sayang
Well, what do you keep from me?
Nah, apa yang Anda simpan dari saya?
I can't say that to you, Osman.
Saya tidak bisa mengatakan itu kepada Anda, Osman.
Honey chick!
Cewek sayang!
How can you not say, Bala chick?
Bagaimana bisa kau tidak bilang, Bala cewek?
I can not say.
Saya tidak bisa mengatakan.
You are good fortune.
Anda adalah keberuntungan.
Informally, I wouldn't want you to be in more danger.
Secara informal, saya tidak ingin Anda berada dalam bahaya yang lebih besar.
He wouldn't want it in my father.
Dia tidak menginginkannya di ayahku.
Let me go.
Biarkan aku pergi.
Bala!
Bala!
Now you will tell me!
Sekarang Anda akan memberi tahu saya!
Where is your father?
Dimana ayahmu
What's going on?
Apa yang terjadi
If you don't say the truth,
Jika Anda tidak mengatakan yang sebenarnya,
... you can't take a single step out of the oba.
... Anda tidak dapat mengambil satu langkah pun dari oba.
When he heard what happened to him, he sent me here.
Ketika dia mendengar apa yang terjadi padanya, dia mengirim saya ke sini.
I realized that he will sacrifice for you.
Saya menyadari bahwa dia akan berkorban untuk Anda.
At that time,...
Lalu, ...
It is in the hands of Yannis.
Itu ada di tangan Yannis.
Osman Bey, who will give Yannis the treasure for you.
Osman Bey, yang akan memberi Yannis harta untukmu.
How does he do that?
Bagaimana dia melakukannya?
Don't you know where he went?
Apakah kamu tidak tahu kemana dia pergi?
Believe me, Osman did not tell me.
Percayalah, Osman tidak memberitahuku.
The last words he said when he was leaving are still in my mind.
Kata-kata terakhir yang dia katakan ketika dia pergi masih ada di pikiranku.
"We came from the ground, we will go to the ground," he said.
"Kami datang dari tanah, kami akan pergi ke tanah," katanya.
Separate clay, ...
Tanah liat terpisah, ...
... to the treasure.
... untuk harta karun.
Edebali.
Edebali.
I understand.
Saya mengerti.
I get it, where it is.
Saya mengerti, di mana tempatnya.
Honey, let it stop informal anxiety.
Sayang, biarkan itu menghentikan kecemasan informal.
I know where your father is.
Saya tahu di mana ayahmu.
How?
Bagaimana?
First of all, let me save Sheikh Edebali from the hands of the noble.
Pertama-tama, izinkan saya menyelamatkan Sheikh Edebali dari tangan para bangsawan.
Then I will want you.
Maka aku akan menginginkanmu.
Let's get this uphill, afterwards, with the permission of Allah.
Mari kita naik ini, setelah itu, dengan izin Allah.
Woe, woe, woe.
Terkutuklah, celakalah, celakalah.
You messed up a bag of figs.
Anda mengacaukan sekantong ara.
You are unable even to taste the victory you have won.
Anda bahkan tidak dapat merasakan kemenangan yang telah Anda menangkan.
This chick is quite with you,
Cewek ini cukup dengan Anda,
... there will be no peace in your room!
... tidak akan ada kedamaian di kamar Anda!
No, Selcan hatun?
Tidak, Selcan hatun?
You try to break my house?
Anda mencoba menghancurkan rumah saya?
No,...
Tidak, ...
... I try to save the kayi oba.
... Saya mencoba menyelamatkan oba kayi.
Selcan yenge!
Selcan yenge!
You came to our guest, ...
Anda datang ke tamu kami, ...
... you're the crown of our heads.
... kau adalah mahkota kepala kita.
Not that,..
Namun, ..
... do not put your nose in the work of the oba.
... jangan taruh hidungmu dalam karya oba.
Otherwise,..
Kalau tidak, ..
... I have to end your stay.
... Saya harus mengakhiri masa tinggal Anda.
Well, ...
Nah, ...
... when the husband becomes,
... ketika sang suami menjadi,
of course there will be someone to rule.
tentu saja akan ada seseorang yang memerintah.
But remember, ...
Tapi ingat, ...
... you are not a gentleman.
... kamu bukan pria sejati.
You're just a proxy.
Anda hanyalah proxy.
fled.
melarikan diri.
Where is Osman, Megala?
Di mana Osman, Megala?
They escaped, sir.
Mereka melarikan diri, tuan.
They killed all our men.
Mereka membunuh semua orang kita.
Attack! Kill them all!
Menyerang! Bunuh mereka semua!
Ya Allah!
Ya allah!
Osman!
Osman!
I grew up, my Sheikh
Saya tumbuh dewasa, Sheikh saya
Sir, very crowded we have to go right away.
Pak, sangat ramai kita harus segera pergi.
You go and I will embroider them.
Anda pergi dan saya akan menyulam mereka.
No.
Tidak ada.
It did not.
Ini tidak.
Rotate more.
Putar lebih banyak.
Look, look ...
Lihat, lihat ...
how excited my Balaam.
betapa bersemangatnya Bileamku.
It did, it did. You are so beautiful, mahal.
Itu benar, benar. Kamu sangat cantik, mahal.
We entered into many dangers, survived all the badges ...
Kami masuk ke banyak bahaya, selamat dari semua lencana ...
... how many times have we returned from death?
... sudah berapa kali kita kembali dari kematian?
Not that,...
Namun, ...
... for the first time, my heart beats Gonca.
... untuk pertama kalinya, jantungku berdetak kencang.
My Almighty Lord has lowered his heart to love fire ...
Tuhanku Yang Mahakuasa telah menurunkan hatinya untuk mencintai api ...
honey from her.
sayang darinya.
I hope it will come with goodness and goodness after that.
Saya berharap itu akan datang dengan kebaikan dan kebaikan setelah itu.
God willing.
Mudah-mudahan.
Selcan hat will be here soon.
Topi Selcan akan segera datang.
My God ...
Tuhan ...
... calm my soul.
... tenang jiwaku.
You're in your father's garden,
Anda berada di kebun ayahmu,
... you are a smile, Bala.
... kamu tersenyum, Bala.
You are his precious.
Anda adalah miliknya yang berharga.
I don't know, Sheikh,
Saya tidak tahu, Sheikh,
... will Osman give you?
... akankah Osman memberimu?
My father, from the treasure he gave his life for,
Ayah saya, dari harta yang ia berikan hidupnya,
Osman gave up for bey.
Osman menyerah untuk bey.
He has revealed his own life.
Dia telah mengungkapkan hidupnya sendiri.
His love for him is clear.
Cintanya untuknya jelas.
This marriage will also please him.
Pernikahan ini juga akan menyenangkannya.
You're right.
Kamu benar
Sheikh2im, Osman does not drop his bravery from his tongue.
Sheikh2im, Osman tidak menjatuhkan keberaniannya dari lidahnya.
He trusts him.
Dia percaya padanya.
He will not entrust you to him for the sake of him.
Dia tidak akan mempercayakan Anda kepadanya demi dia.
Let's look at that time, ...
Mari kita lihat waktu itu, ...
... your first child ...
... anak pertamamu ...
Do you want a boy or a girl?
Apakah Anda menginginkan anak laki-laki atau perempuan?
I would like to have a good son, Gonca.
Saya ingin memiliki putra yang baik, Gonca.
My Lord, everything to our last breath,
Tuhanku, segalanya untuk nafas terakhir kita,
... I wish you good luck.
... Semoga beruntung.
God willing.
Mudah-mudahan.
Because of us, there is a pusat ...
Karena kita, ada pusat ...
... you're on the brink of death.
... Anda berada di ambang kematian.
Exist, Osman.
Ada, Osman.
I surrounded my pusat.
Saya mengelilingi pusat saya.
However, I heard that ...
Namun, saya mendengar bahwa ...
... you have thrown yourself in the lap of my life for me, Edebali.
... Anda telah melemparkan diri Anda di pangkuan hidup saya untuk saya, Edebali.
They tortured you a lot.
Mereka banyak menyiksamu.
How did you get out of that cender?
Bagaimana Anda bisa keluar dari cender itu?
From that dark well that I fell ...
Dari sumur gelap itu aku jatuh ...
... I came out of your light, Edebali.
... Saya keluar dari cahaya Anda, Edebali.
The skill is not caring ...
Keterampilannya tidak peduli ...
... sees son.
... melihat anak laki-laki.
As you can see, ...
Seperti yang Anda lihat, ...
... that light is at your core.
... Cahaya itu adalah inti Anda.
God willing,...
Mudah-mudahan, ...
... This light will illuminate the horizon of Oghuz.
... Cahaya ini akan menerangi cakrawala Oghuz.
At that time,...
Lalu, ...
What is this darkness in my heart?
Apakah kegelapan ini di hati saya?
Why did you delay me when I came to your threshold?
Mengapa Anda menunda saya ketika saya sampai di ambang pintu Anda?
Don't put me off, ...
Jangan tinggalkan aku, ...
... the solution flies more than the wounds in my flesh.
... solusinya terbang lebih dari luka di dagingku.
Excuse my cruelty, my toy.
Maafkan kekejaman saya, mainan saya.
Forgive me.
Maafkan aku.
My Sheikh, Edebali.
Sheikh saya, Edebali.
I...
Saya ...
I'm not a forgiveness.
Saya bukan pengampunan.
But I know that ...
Tapi saya tahu itu ...
... seeking goodness in himself,
... mencari kebaikan dalam dirinya sendiri,
... finds the truth in his heart, son.
... menemukan kebenaran di dalam hatinya, Nak.
Your road is beautiful, ...
Jalanmu indah, ...
... your intention is majestic.
... niatmu agung.
As long as,...
Selama ...
... preserving its essence, ...
... menjaga esensinya, ...
... keep your ore.
... simpan bijihmu.
Father!
Ayah!
Who did this to you?
Siapa yang melakukan ini padamu?
Osman.
Osman.
Call a physician immediately!
Panggil dokter segera!
Megale ...
Megale ...
Megala is dead, my daughter.
Megala sudah mati, putriku.
Don't worry, sir.
Jangan khawatir, tuan.
We will take our revenge.
Kami akan membalas dendam kami.
What the hell happened?
Apa yang terjadi?
Where's the literary?
Di mana sastra?
Where is Osman?
Dimanakah Osman?
Everything is now exposed.
Semuanya sekarang terbuka.
My daughter...
Putri saya ...
... after that there is only blood.
... setelah itu hanya ada darah.
Master Yannis.
Tuan Yannis.
Boğan paid the price of his own stupidity.
Boğan membayar harga kebodohannya sendiri.
What about you, Salvador?
Bagaimana denganmu, Salvador?
What will you pay for your incompetence?
Apa yang akan Anda bayar atas ketidakmampuan Anda?
This is the misfortune of Bogan, Kalanos.
Ini adalah kemalangan Bogan, Kalanos.
However, in Kulucahisar castle ...
Namun, di kastil Kulucahisar ...
... the clumsy live long.
... kikuk hidup lama.
What do you want to say, Salvador?
Apa yang ingin kamu katakan, Salvador?
It is clear what I want to say.
Jelas apa yang ingin saya katakan.
While I was a bounty hunter with my men,
Sementara saya adalah pemburu hadiah dengan anak buah saya,
..joyful...
... ..you
Enough!
Cukup!
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
I was relieved.
Saya merasa lega.
You did this.
Kamu melakukan ini.
I did, father, bon appetit healing.
Saya lakukan, ayah, penyembuhan nafsu makan.
It resembles the rose sherbet of the deceased mother.
Itu menyerupai serbat mawar dari ibu yang sudah meninggal.
May my Lord fill the graves of light, I hope.
Semoga Tuhanku mengisi kuburan cahaya, kuharap.
God willing.
Mudah-mudahan.
What a beautiful son you left me and you went ...
Apa anak yang cantik kau meninggalkanku dan kau pergi ...
Ulduz chick.
Cewek ulduz.
God's friends,
Teman tuhan,
... be a neighbor.
... jadilah tetangga.
Dad how are you
Ayah, bagaimana kabarmu?
I couldn't get enough of all this.
Saya tidak bisa mendapatkan cukup dari semua ini.
Osman Bey survived ...
Osman Bey selamat ...
... is safe in the treasury.
... aman di perbendaharaan.
Thank god.
Syukurlah.
Mr. Osman awaits more and more troubles.
Pak Osman menunggu lebih banyak masalah.
May my Lord be his deputy.
Semoga Tuhanku menjadi wakilnya.
Amine.
Amin.
I want to say something to you.
Saya ingin mengatakan sesuatu kepada Anda.
But I'm afraid.
Tapi saya takut.
Don't hesitate, my rose face girl.
Jangan ragu, gadis wajah mawar saya.
lest.
jangan.
Mr. Osman...
Osman Bey ...
Osman bey said ...
Osman bey berkata ...
Well, my daughter.
Nah, putriku.
What did Osman Bey say?
Apa yang dikatakan Osman Bey?
Selcan would send his chick.
Selcan akan mengirim ceweknya.
To ask me.
Untuk bertanya kepada saya.
Subhane rabbike rabbil izma amma yesifun, ...
Subhane rabbike rabbil izma amma yesifun, ...
... and then you know, allel murselin ...
... dan kemudian Anda tahu, allel murselin ...
... the hamdülil lahi rabbil realm.
... alam hamdülil lahi rabbil.
Al Fatiha.
El Fatiha.
Kanturalı ...
Kanturalı ...
...my brother.
... saudara saya.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Siblings!
Saudara!
We will take your revenge.
Kami akan membalas dendam Anda.
We'll get ..
Kita akan ..
They will drown in the blood they shed, bro.
Mereka akan tenggelam dalam darah yang mereka tumpahkan, kawan.
Our blood will not stay anywhere.
Darah kita tidak akan tinggal di mana pun.
These lands ...
Tanah ini ...
... until he became a dorm ...
... sampai dia menjadi asrama ...
... many coaches ...
... banyak pelatih ...
... they watered the land with their blood.
... mereka menyirami tanah dengan darah mereka.
Nice fathers ...
Ayah yang baik ...
... son of ...
... anak ...
... into the soil with your own hands ...
... ke tanah dengan tanganmu sendiri ...
... they entrusted it.
... mereka mempercayakannya.
Nice love is incomplete.
Cinta yang bagus tidak lengkap.
No.
Tidak ada.
It...
Ini ...
is not a dry country fight.
bukan pertarungan negara kering.
These souls ...
Jiwa-jiwa ini ...
... with a coin account ...
... dengan akun koin ...
... ambitious pastures were not wasted with love.
... padang rumput yang ambisius tidak disia-siakan dengan cinta.
This fight ...
Pertarungan ini ...
... is a fight between truth and superstition.
... adalah pertarungan antara kebenaran dan takhayul.
Until the superstition is completely zailed ...
Sampai takhayul benar-benar dihujani ...
... We will not stop!
... Kami tidak akan berhenti!
We will not stop, Osman.
Kami tidak akan berhenti, Osman.
We will not stop!
Kami tidak akan berhenti!
We will not give up!
Kami tidak akan menyerah!
God's true religion ...
Agama sejati Tuhan ...
... until the judge ...
... sampai hakim ...
... our pusat will not be in the case!
... pusat kami tidak akan ada dalam kasing!
This fight ...
Pertarungan ini ...
... crossing the cross ...
... menyeberang salib ...
... is the fight of the crescent!
... adalah pertarungan bulan sabit!
Allahu Akbar!
Allahu Akbar!
Welcome, Selcan hatun.
Selamat datang, Selcan hatun.
Good to see you.
Saya melihatnya bagus.
I would like to see Sheikh Edebali.
Saya ingin melihat Sheikh Edebali.
I have something to say to him.
Saya ingin mengatakan sesuatu kepadanya.
It is in prayer to the honor of our martyrs.
Itu adalah dalam doa untuk kehormatan para martir kita.
You wait a little.
Tunggu sebentar.
Finally, we could see his face laughing like this, Osman.
Akhirnya, kita bisa melihat wajahnya tertawa seperti ini, Osman.
What is the reason for this state?
Apa alasan untuk kondisi ini?
Say and we'll be happy too.
Katakan dan kami akan senang juga.
I wait for Selcan aunt Aygül.
Saya menunggu bibi Selcan Aygül.
For me...
Untuk saya ...
... Bala went to ask for his chick.
... Bala pergi untuk meminta ceweknya.
Is that so?
Benarkah begitu?
May Allah make you happy.
Semoga Allah membuatmu bahagia.
Complete it all.
Lengkapi semuanya.
Amine.
Amin.
Hopefully Bala's chick and her father ...
Semoga cewek Bala dan ayahnya ...
... does not cause big trouble.
... tidak menyebabkan masalah besar.
But you know, ...
Tapi tahukah Anda, ...
... the bad luck has been on us since they came to our oba.
... nasib buruk telah menimpa kita sejak mereka datang ke oba kita.
Don't say that, Aygül.
Jangan katakan itu, Aygül.
The bad luck spreads from Kulucahisar, where the shroud is nested.
Nasib buruk menyebar dari Kulucahisar, tempat kafan bersarang.
God...
Tuhan ...
... don't let the literature go away.
... jangan biarkan lektur pergi.
As for honeymoon ...
Adapun bulan madu ...
... don't take her name like that in your mouth.
... jangan menyebut namanya seperti itu di mulutmu.
I don't want to break your heart.
Saya tidak ingin menghancurkan hatimu.
Well, Osman.
Baiklah, Osman.
Well.
Nah.
Won't you wish me happiness?
Tidakkah Anda berharap saya bahagia?
Fastest time...
Waktu tesis ...
... We will have a wedding ceremony with Alişar bey.
... Kami akan mengadakan upacara pernikahan dengan Alişar bey.
Non,...
Informal, ...
... you are the pearl of our obese.
... Anda adalah mutiara dari obesitas kami.
Me too...
Aku juga ...
... in this world and ...
... di dunia ini dan ...
... you are my sister in the hereafter.
... kamu adalah adikku di akhirat.
God,...
Tuhan ...
... your home
... rumahmu
... let it be the happiest.
... biarlah yang paling bahagia.
Always...
Selalu ...
... happy, happy.
... bahagia, bahagia.
Welcome, good luck, Selcan hatun.
Selamat datang, semoga sukses, Selcan hatun.
I saw nice, my beautiful girl.
Saya melihat baik, gadis cantik saya.
I saw you like this or I became even more happy.
Saya melihat Anda seperti ini atau saya menjadi lebih bahagia.
Thank God we've survived the problems.
Alhamdulillah kita sudah selamat dari masalah.
We will see even better days, evelallah.
Kita akan melihat hari yang lebih baik lagi, evelallah.
I came to meet with Sheikh Edebali.
Saya datang untuk bertemu dengan Sheikh Edebali.
For a good job.
Untuk pekerjaan yang bagus.
Here, Selcan hatun.
Di sini, Selcan hatun.
Your eyes are enlightened, Balaam.
Mata Anda adalah Bileam yang tercerahkan.
May Allah grant you to chop your wedding in time.
Semoga Allah memberi Anda waktu untuk memotong pernikahan Anda.
Aygul?
Aygul?
What happened again?
Apa yang terjadi lagi?
Nothing, mom.
Tidak ada apa-apa, bu.
Nothing, why would you shed a tear?
Tidak ada, mengapa Anda meneteskan air mata?
Say it to me.
Katakan itu padaku.
Mom, I know you'll be angry.
Bu, aku tahu kamu akan marah.
But I can't help it.
Tapi aku tidak bisa menahannya.
Osman.
Osman.
What did he do?
Apa yang dia lakukan?
What did he say upset you?
Apa yang dia katakan membuatmu kesal?
She didn't do anything to me, mom.
Dia tidak melakukan apa pun padaku, bu.
Selcan hatun ...
Selcan hatun ...
Selcan hatun went to meet with Edebali.
Selcan hatun pergi menemui Edebali.
What is he doing to the chick at the inn?
Apa yang dia lakukan pada cewek di penginapan?
And what will he meet with Edebeli?
Dan apa yang akan dia temui dengan Edebeli?
Honey chick.
Cewek sayang
Osman would want the Bala line.
Osman menginginkan garis Bala.
Especially ...
Terutama ...
... was it up to her sister-in-law to ask a girl for Osman while her uncle was standing?
... apakah kakak ipar perempuannya meminta Osman sementara pamannya berdiri?
They were all surprised.
Mereka semua terkejut.
Wipe away the tear.
Seka air mata.
You're like this today because you dreamed of nothing.
Anda seperti ini hari ini karena Anda tidak memimpikan apa pun.
Your fortune is bright girl.
Keberuntunganmu adalah gadis yang cerdas.
The huge starboard is the brain ...
Starboard besar adalah otak ...
... you will be a babe to your mansion.
... Anda akan menjadi bayi ke rumah Anda.
If Osman goes with this head ...
Jika Osman pergi dengan kepala ini ...
... both to himself and around ...
... baik untuk dirinya sendiri dan sekitar ...
... will bring nothing but trouble.
... akan membawa apa-apa selain masalah.
That he will cry like a spian,
Bahwa dia akan menangis seperti orang Spanyol,
... thank the yacht get up.
... terima kasih yacht bangun.
Finally, we have survived a difficult test Selcan hatun.
Akhirnya, kami berhasil melewati ujian Hatcan Selcan yang sulit.
Thank you.
Terima kasih
My God...
Tuhanku ...
... salute our hearts the next way.
... salut hati kita dengan cara berikutnya.
Amine.
Amin.
Praise be to Allah, of course.
Segala puji bagi Allah, tentu saja.
However, you are not paid.
Namun, Anda tidak dibayar.
You have claimed my Ottoman.
Anda telah mengklaim Ottoman saya.
You guarded and watched.
Anda berjaga dan menyaksikan.
God bless you.
Tuhan memberkatimu
Yiğit is not alone, Selcan hatun.
Yiğit tidak sendirian, Selcan hatun.
Even though no one is with you ...
Meskipun tidak ada yang bersamamu ...
... the way of walking with Allah ...
... cara berjalan dengan Allah ...
... necessarily gets better.
... tentu saja menjadi lebih baik.
We didn't do anything.
Kami tidak melakukan apa-apa.
Whatever happened is right.
Apa pun yang terjadi adalah benar.
Osman in our son ...
Osman di putra kami ...
... survived with faith ...
... selamat dengan iman ...
... from this struggle ...
... dari perjuangan ini ...
... survived with the belief.
... selamat dengan keyakinan.
Sir,...
Pak, ...
... you tell Osman to my son.
... Anda memberitahu Osman kepada anak saya.
We would also like to say that our daughter is a Bala woman.
Kami juga ingin mengatakan bahwa putri kami adalah wanita Bala.
Bala chick is very well bred, ...
Bala cewek dibesarkan dengan sangat baik, ...
... is a very beautiful girl.
... adalah gadis yang sangat cantik.
If you have permission ...
Jika Anda memiliki izin ...
... we want to illuminate our obese with light.
... kami ingin menerangi obesitas kami dengan cahaya.
Allah's command, with the prophet's tribe ...
Perintah Allah, dengan suku nabi ...
... your daughter Honeymoon ...
... Putrimu berbulan madu ...
... we want our son Osmana.
... kami ingin putra kami Osmana.
Thank you, chick.
Terima kasih cewek.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
I mean something, dad.
Maksud saya sesuatu, ayah.
Is there permission?
Apakah ada izin?
Come on girl.
Ayo gadis.
Here you go.
Di sini Anda pergi.
I thought about what you said, dad.
Saya memikirkan apa yang Anda katakan, ayah.
If you see fit ...
Jika Anda cocok ...
... I have my consent with Alişar bey.
... Saya mendapat persetujuan saya dengan Alişar bey.
Is this your consent, girl?
Apakah ini persetujuan Anda, nona?
Does me or your mother have an internal?
Apakah saya atau ibu Anda memiliki internal?
Be sure no dad.
Pastikan tidak ada ayah.
First of all, obam comes.
Pertama-tama, obam datang.
I know that ...
Saya tahu itu ...
... my obba and my family's fortune are in trouble.
... Obba saya dan kekayaan keluarga saya dalam kesulitan.
OK then,...
Bagaimana dengan ...
What about your fortune?
Bagaimana dengan keberuntunganmu?
My good fortune,
Keberuntungan saya,
... in your happiness, dad.
... dalam kebahagiaanmu, ayah.
Give me the best about God, girl.
Beri aku yang terbaik tentang Tuhan, gadis.
This crunchy happiness to you, ....
Kebahagiaan renyah ini untuk Anda, ....
... hopefully bring strength and strength to our obese.
... semoga membawa kekuatan dan kekuatan untuk obesitas kita.
God willing.
Mudah-mudahan.
We also set up the nest,
Kami juga menyiapkan sarang,
... protects sooner.
... melindungi lebih cepat.
If you wish a happy marriage ...
Jika Anda menginginkan pernikahan yang bahagia ...
... Do not forget you.
... Jangan lupa Anda.
Smokeless chimney, ...
Cerobong tanpa asap, ...
... no husband without wife, my daughter.
... tidak ada suami tanpa istri, putriku.
You hung your love in my heart.
Kamu menggantung cintamu di hatiku.
Non,...
Informal, ...
... beyond you ...
... di luar dirimu ...
... it is death, Bala chick.
... itu adalah kematian, Bala cewek.
Our Almighty Lord has commanded his servants to marry.
Tuhan kita Yang Mahakuasa telah memerintahkan hamba-hambanya untuk menikah.
Installing a home is destined.
Menginstal rumah ditakdirkan.
And certainly at the wedding ...
Dan tentu saja di pesta pernikahan ...
... there is miracle.
... ada keajaiban.
Osman bey wrist brace,
Osman bey wrist brace,
his heart is fearless.
hatinya tak kenal takut.
I know.
Aku tahu.
The brave young man is a fierce warrior.
Pemuda pemberani itu adalah pejuang yang ganas.
As for honeymoon ...
Adapun bulan madu ...
... Bala ...
... Bala ...
... raised in the way of Allah ...
... dibesarkan di jalan Allah ...
... is the head of the smokers.
... adalah kepala para perokok.
Sure, I'd like to set up a home one day.
Tentu, saya ingin mendirikan rumah suatu hari nanti.
Not that,...
Namun, ...
... marriage requires bail.
... pernikahan membutuhkan jaminan.
If there is no surety ...
Jika tidak ada jaminan ...
... trouble arises.
... timbul masalah.
That is what I mean ...
Itu yang saya maksud ...
... Osman and Bala ...
... Osman dan Bala ...
... is not equivalent.
... tidak setara.
I don't want to break my heart.
Saya tidak ingin menghancurkan hati saya.
Not that,...
Namun, ...
... I do not consent to this.
... Saya tidak menyetujui ini.
Kara Osmanim.
Kara Osmanim.
You have no appetite?
Anda tidak nafsu makan?
So just stands in front of you?
Jadi berdiri saja di depan Anda?
No, no.
Tidak, tidak
The fluttering of his heart comes to my ears, Osman.
Jantungnya berdebar kencang di telingaku, Osman.
(Laughing)
(Tertawa)
Well, Mr. Bamsi.
Baiklah, Tuan Bamsi.
Is it a matter of appetite?
Apakah ini masalah nafsu makan?
Put a wedding on it, ...
Menempatkan pernikahan di atasnya, ...
... I'll show everyone how to hit the sword.
... Aku akan menunjukkan pada semua orang bagaimana cara menghantam pedang.
Vote...
Suara ...
Vote my pusat sharp black Osman.
Pilih pusat saya Osman hitam yang tajam.
You grew up now ...
Kamu tumbuh sekarang ...
... do you wait for the wedding news?
... apakah Anda menunggu berita pernikahan?
Best of all, this job is over ...
Yang terbaik dari semuanya, pekerjaan ini selesai ...
... knocked forty coaches in front of the bed ...
... mengetuk empat puluh pelatih di depan tempat tidur ...
... if I don't turn the obo into an end-to-end familiar.
... jika saya tidak mengubah obo menjadi akrab ujung ke ujung.
Sama sergeant!
Sersan yang sama!
It'd be nice if we had a head on you.
Akan lebih baik jika kami memiliki kepala pada Anda.
Relation Honor brother.
Relation Honor brother.
Sama brain pusat is again moist.
Sama otak pusat lagi lembab.
You can eat in front of you alps.
Anda bisa makan di depan Anda juga.
Everybody eat in front of you.
Semua orang makan di depanmu.
Erkut Alp!
Alp Erkut!
You have no sound, no?
Anda tidak memiliki suara, bukan?
Let him go, Abdurrahman Gazi.
Biarkan dia pergi, Abdurrahman Gazi.
If it is up to him, he will marry us all, so that he can eat a folder.
Jika terserah dia, dia akan menikahi kita semua, sehingga dia bisa makan folder.
(Laughing)
(Tertawa)
Aunt.
Bibi.
No aunty?
Tidak bibi
What is this situation?
Situasi apa ini
Osmar my ...
Osmar saya ...
... Sheikh Edebali ...
... Sheikh Edebali ...
... did not see fit.
... tidak cocok.
There is no consent, he says.
Tidak ada persetujuan, katanya.